[
  {
      "questionNo": "Q1",
      "question": "Ruby had 18 books and donated 15 books. How many books are left with Ruby?",
      "options": [
          "2",
          "3",
          "4",
          "5"
      ],
      "correct": 1
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q2",
      "question": "Ruby had 20 toys. She donated 10 toys. How many toys are left with Ruby?",
      "options": [
          "8",
          "10",
          "11",
          "9"
      ],
      "correct": 1
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q3",
      "question": "Ruby had 22 pairs of shoes. She donated 11 pairs. How many pairs of shoes are left with Ruby?",
      "options": [
          "13",
          "12",
          "10",
          "11"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q4",
      "question": "Helping Hands Club collected 19 blankets. They donated 17 blankets. How many blankets are left?",
      "options": [
          "2",
          "3",
          "4",
          "6"
      ],
      "correct": 0
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q5",
      "question": "The club had 34 craft kits and donated 31 craft kits. How many craft kits are left with them?",
      "options": [
          "4",
          "2",
          "5",
          "3"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q6",
      "question": "Helping Hands Club had 39 teddy bears. They donated 27 teddy bears. How many teddy bears are left with them?",
      "options": [
          "10",
          "13",
          "11",
          "12"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q7",
      "question": "Ruby had 29 school bags. She donated 18 school bags. How many school bags are left with Ruby?",
      "options": [
          "11",
          "10",
          "12",
          "9"
      ],
      "correct": 0
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q8",
      "question": "Rubyâ€™s Helping Hands Club collected 25 coats. They donated 5 coats. How many coats are left?",
      "options": [
          "19",
          "20",
          "17",
          "18"
      ],
      "correct": 1
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q9",
      "question": "Club had 32 pairs of gloves. They donated 11 pairs. How many pairs of gloves are left?",
      "options": [
          "16",
          "18",
          "19",
          "21"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q10",
      "question": "The club had 41 pencils. They donated 30 pencils. How many pencils are left with them?",
      "options": [
          "10",
          "12",
          "11",
          "13"
      ],
      "correct": 2
  }
]
